<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="https://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="https://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Meaghan Lemon &#8211; Evelyn Loves Lemon</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/meaghan/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Botanical Designs</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 18:04:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.25</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Honoring Beauty</title>
		<link>/2016/04/25/honoring-beauty/</link>
		<comments>/2016/04/25/honoring-beauty/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 21:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Meaghan Lemon]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Flowers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Honor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inspiration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Passion]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=124</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Since I started my business I have been getting the question, who is Evelyn? The short answer is, Evelyn is my Grandmother. Like most people with nine decades behind them, she was many things in her life. She is an artist, a mother of seven children (including my father), and a wife to her husband <a href="/2016/04/25/honoring-beauty/" rel="nofollow"><span class="sr-only">Read more about Honoring Beauty</span>[&#8230;]</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since I started my business I have been getting the question, who is Evelyn? The short answer is, Evelyn is my Grandmother. Like most people with nine decades behind them, she was many things in her life. She is an artist, a mother of seven children (including my father), and a wife to her husband Alfred for over sixty years. The one thing she has always been and continues to be is, beautiful.</p>
<div id="attachment_138" style="width: 1428px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy.jpg"><img class="wp-image-138 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy.jpg" alt="My grandmother Evelyn on her wedding day." width="1418" height="1747" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy.jpg 1418w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy-244x300.jpg 244w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy-831x1024.jpg 831w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/evy-500x616.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 1418px) 100vw, 1418px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">My grandmother Evelyn on her wedding day.</p></div>
<p>Anyone who knows my Grandmother would agree she is a beautiful woman. However, her beauty is not conventional or typical. Her beauty comes from within and reflects off every interaction she shares with another. Her celebration of beauty is graceful and organic, but not at all quiet. It shows through in her style of clothes, her bold earrings, and her signature color red. My Grandmother’s ability to create and appreciate beauty has always inspired me.</p>
<div id="attachment_129" style="width: 2336px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016.jpg"><img class="wp-image-129 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016.jpg" alt="Peonies painted by my grandmother" width="2326" height="1857" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016.jpg 2326w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016-300x240.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016-1024x818.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2016/04/IMG_1016-500x399.jpg 500w" sizes="(max-width: 2326px) 100vw, 2326px" /></a><p class="wp-caption-text">Peonies painted by my grandmother</p></div>
<p>There was a time in my life when I struggled with what my appreciation for beauty meant. At times, I felt like I would be judged as vain or shallow if I gave too much time and energy to esthetics. This left me feeling conflicted because naturally, I was drawn to creating beautiful things. Having my Grandmother as an example helped me settle that conflict. There was nothing shallow or silly about her. She celebrated beauty and there was nothing vain or arrogant about the way she did it. My Grandmother taught me how to honor the beauty in life, and for that I am forever grateful.</p>
<p>When it came time to decide on a name for my new business, it only seemed natural to use Evelyn. Her example has been an endless supply of inspiration and education. Without her, I am not sure I would have had the courage to embrace the beauty that truly moves me. I owe my Grandmother much more but using her name was my way of honoring the beauty I see in her.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/2016/04/25/honoring-beauty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sharing My Joy</title>
		<link>/2016/03/24/sharing-my-joy/</link>
		<comments>/2016/03/24/sharing-my-joy/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2016 01:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Meaghan Lemon]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Flowers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Passion]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://localhost:8888/?p=5</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[From the time I was a little girl being in the garden or smelling a bouquet of fresh flowers has brought me pure joy. The kind of joy that sinks so deep inside of you, it plants itself and never leaves. I spent most of my childhood playing outside collecting all the beautiful things nature <a href="/2016/03/24/sharing-my-joy/" rel="nofollow"><span class="sr-only">Read more about Sharing My Joy</span>[&#8230;]</a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the time I was a little girl being in the garden or smelling a bouquet of fresh flowers has brought me pure joy. The kind of joy that sinks so deep inside of you, it plants itself and never leaves. I spent most of my childhood playing outside collecting all the beautiful things nature has to offer.  Filling my hands with dirt, sticking my nose in a blossoming magnolia or running my bare feet across a fresh covering of moss. This was my heaven. Every summer I would go back to the same places where I could find wild sweet peas growing or endless patches of forget me not’s. These were the simple joys that called to me. </p>
<p>As I grew older these simple pleasures began to get pushed aside by my need to be sensible and productive. I chose to work towards a degree that would provide a job. I married. I worked. I paid bills. I felt… nothing. Until, the moment I got a whiff of fresh soil or held a cut flower in my hand. That joy that was planted so deep inside of me would sprout up and I would feel alive. </p>
<p>Each time these little pangs of joy knocked at my heart it became harder to ignore. I began to work in my garden as much as possible, I would bring fresh flowers home just to rearrange them through out the week. These moments brought me joy even in times when things seemed hopeless. I knew there was something to this.  </p>
<p>I remember reading somewhere that you should pay attention to what makes you cry. If watching someone race across a finish line brings a tear to your eye, you might want to go out and buy some running shoes. A few years back, on a day I was not feeling so joyful, I was sitting on a bench feeling the weight of all my life choices. When a little girl came up to me with a little flower she had picked from the ground and said this is for you. That same spot my joy had been planted was now flooded with grief and gratitude. My eyes filled with tears and I knew what I had to do. </p>
<p>I began to enroll in some local design classes. I filled my house with cut flowers. Sometimes I would leave an arrangement on a friend’s doorstep. In these small acts I began to grow my joy into something worth sharing. People may take notice if you are good at what you do but people are affected when you do it with joy. Part of giving back to this world is finding that place deep inside where your joy is planted. You must grow it and tend to it. Finally, you must share it. So others can recognize what joy looks like and maybe even find theirs.        </p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/2016/03/24/sharing-my-joy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>11</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
